That fucking
prostitute…
Didn't it go
as you planned?
Why are you so upset?
This is not enough
Hey, why do you hate
Shin Yoo-il so much?
I told you
- Shin Yoo-il, that guy…
- He disbanded the group?
Honestly, you should
be grateful to him
If it weren't for him
you'd already have…
I'd already have what?
I wasn't a mess
like this before that
This is all…
because of
that bastard!
Hey, Choi Hyobum
It was you, right?
You spread the video
What the fuck?
Are you damn crazy?
Are you crazy? What the
fuck are you doing?
You're the crazy one!
You crafty pervert
You secretly filmed it
and spread it, didn't you?
Do you have proof?
Proof?
Yeah, I have plenty
for your dirty deed
I don't care whatever
you do with Shin Yoo-il
but if you touch
Hyesung again
then
I'll send you to hell
Got it?
Fucking bastard!
Stop there
you bastard!
Come here, you asshole!